bring fat welcome to another installment
欢迎来到另一批
of spring tips in this installment we're
在这一期的 spring 技巧 中，我们是
gonna look at the new Olaf client
来看看新的Olaf客户
support in spring security 5 now in a
在Spring Security 5中提供支持
previous installment we looked at spring
上一期文章我们看了春季
security Olaf and we looked at the OAuth
安全性Olaf，我们研究了OAuth
authorization server that you could
您可以的授权服务器
create pretty easily using spring
使用spring轻松创建
security now that support that
现在的安全性
fundamental support inside of spring
Spring 内部的基本支撑
security OAuth has been there for a
安全性OAuth已经存在
while and for those who are playing the
而对于那些正在玩
home game it can be kind of confusing to
家用游戏可能会使您感到困惑
to sort of figure out where we are in
弄清楚我们在哪里
terms of the OAuth picture and spring so
OAuth图片的条款，因此
let's have a quick review right well we
让我们快速浏览一下吧
it all started with spring security off
一切始于Spring Security
which is a third-party project a
这是一个第三方项目
community project that we then brought
然后我们带来的社区项目
into the spring portfolio and we've
进入春季投资组合，我们已经
developed pretty consistently since 2011
自2011年以来发展稳定
that project has been gonna gone on to a
该项目将继续进行
underpin the UAA the authorization
支持UAA授权
server the identity provider that we
服务器我们的身份提供者
provide for carpentry our open-source
为木工提供我们的开源
platform so that that component has been
平台，以便该组件已经
battle tested at scale by enterprise
企业进行了大规模测试
customers for for you know years five
客户为您所知五年
six years now in in production the UAA
UAA已投入生产六年
is a hub if you will you can use it to
是集线器，如果您愿意，可以使用它来
talk to other things like Active
与其他活动交谈
Directory and and so on now that is an
目录等，现在是
open to project and the ninety percent
开放项目，百分之九十
of that work that's in the ua is is back
在UA中的工作又回来了
in the spring security sort of a roth
在春季的安全保障中
project right that project has always
该项目始终具有的项目权利
had several different bits it's the
有几个不同的地方
ability to stand up an OAuth server and
能够站起来的OAuth服务器和
the ability to act as a client to an
充当客户的能力
OAuth service and that's important when
OAuth服务，这在以下情况下很重要
we talk about OAuth the client is is
我们谈论的OAuth客户端是
arguably the most important part of the
可以说是最重要的部分
protocol o auth of course is a protocol
协议o auth当然是协议
for authentication delegation there are
对于身份验证委派有
three different pieces that we care
我们关心的三个不同部分
about or actual I suppose there's four
大概或实际我想有四个
there's the authorization server the
有授权服务器
thing that vens tokens that we can then
提供代币的东西，然后我们就可以
use to then make requests of other
用于随后提出其他要求
resources that are protected and require
受保护且需要的资源
those those tokens so that's a REST API
这些令牌，这就是REST API
maybe a facebook friend graph that kind
也许是Facebook好友图
of thing the Twitter timeline API and
Twitter时间轴API和
these different API s require token so
这些不同的API需要令牌，因此
we call them resource servers okay so
我们称它们为资源服务器，所以
the authorization server ven's resource
授权服务器的资源
authorization and access tokens that
授权和访问令牌
then can be used to talk to resource
然后可以用来与资源交谈
service a client is the one that bears
为客户服务是一个承担的人
that token on behalf of the user so you
该令牌代表用户，因此您
have a user driving a client and there
有一个用户在驱动客户
can be one user and multiple clients you
可以是一个用户，也可以是多个客户端
might have for example Facebook on the
例如在
on the iPhone versus Facebook in the
在iPhone和Facebook中
html5 browser versus Facebook on the on
html5浏览器与Facebook
the Android device all three of the all
所有这三个Android设备
threes are all three of these are
三分全都三个
different client experiences but it's
不同的客户体验，但这是
fun eventually ultimately me who's
最终我很有趣
driving that experience when I log in as
当我以
my facebook profile or Twitter profile
我的Facebook个人资料或Twitter个人资料
or whatever right these are these four
或者这四个是正确的
pieces make up the topology of an
件组成一个拓扑
average of architecture now as often is
现在的建筑平均水平是
not we are used to thinking about the
不是我们习惯于思考
resource server and the authorization
资源服务器和授权
server as being the same thing when you
当您将服务器视为同一件事
think about Facebook it's the same set
想想Facebook是同一个场景
of API so you get a token from there
API，因此您可以从那里获得令牌
OAuth API is and then you use that token
OAuth API是，然后您使用该令牌
to then call the Facebook friend graph
然后调用Facebook好友图
but there is no reason that this has to
但这没有理由
be you could for example use a a ooofff
例如，您可以使用aa ooofff
token an access token from an
令牌来自
authorization server to to then call
授权服务器然后调用
some other third party service or it's a
其他一些第三方服务，或者是
to call another resource service right
调用另一个资源服务权限
so you know you you may delegate
所以你知道你可以委托
authentication in this case as a
在这种情况下，身份验证为
resource server you may delegate
您可以委派的资源服务器
authentication to some other thing when
对其他事物进行身份验证
you do that now spring security huh oh
你现在就做那 Spring 的安全吧
uh intern was we saw Auto configured
实习生，我们看到自动配置了
support for it in spring boots so you
在 spring boot 中支持它，所以你
can use spring boot to auto configure
可以使用Spring Boot自动配置
ooofff clients and then going step
ooofff客户，然后再走一步
further there are some other use cases
此外还有其他一些用例
related to protecting resources and to
与保护资源和
perpetuating access tokens that we saw
我们看到的永久性访问令牌
Auto configured and spring clad which
自动配置和Spring 包覆
built upon the support in spring boot
建立在 spring boot 的支撑上
and that's that's basically the story
这就是基本上的故事
that's we've had so far up until spring
那就是我们直到 Spring 为止
security 5 so spring security 5 is the
安全5因此，Spring Security 5是
first release of spring security to come
即将发布的Spring Security 防护
after Spring Framework 5 which itself
在Spring Framework 5之后
introduces a one major theme which is
介绍一个主要主题是
the new reactive programming support and
新的反应式编程支持和
a number of other smaller things the
其他一些较小的东西
reactive programming in of itself would
反应式编程本身
be enough I would think to justify a
我想足以证明一个理由
brand-new spring security release but
全新的Spring Security 发布，但
never
决不
content descent on their laurels the
他们的月桂树含量下降
spring security team have two major
Spring Security 团队有两个主要
features that are in this new release
此新版本中的功能
with much more to come in in 5.1 the the
还有更多的5.1
first major feature is integration and
第一个主要功能是集成和
support for reactive programming and
支持反应式编程和
spring security five and that's all
Spring Security 五，仅此而已
that's a whole you know other spring tip
这是一个整体，你知道其他的 Spring 技巧
and and then also support for OAuth
然后还支持OAuth
there's some other really nice features
还有其他一些非常好的功能
as well there's support for example
还有例如支持
there's a new password encryption sort
有一个新的密码加密排序
of a hierarchy there that's really kind
真的很友善
of convenient there's a lot of nice
方便的地方很多
stuff there just to improve testing
在那里只是为了改善测试
support so a lot of convenient features
支持这么多方便的功能
in spring security five for the two big
在Spring Security 五为两大
ones are this new support for acting as
这些是作为
an OAuth client and the reactive
OAuth客户端和反应式
programming support and in this
编程支持，在此
installment of spring tips we're gonna
我们将要介绍的 spring 技巧
look at the OAuth client support now
现在看看OAuth客户端支持
when I say client again we've already
当我再次说客户时，我们已经
talked about in a previous installment
在上一期中谈到
how to stand up a spring security OAuth
如何站起Spring Security OAuth
authorization server and I've got
授权服务器，我有
something that's basically similar to
基本上类似于
that running in the background here I'll
在这里在后台运行
leave it to you to consult the code in
留给您查阅代码
the spring tips get repository for
Spring 的提示获取资源库
spring security OAuth spring security
Spring Security 性OAuthSpring Security 性
500 worth client there's a repo there
500位有价值的客户那里有一个回购协议
under the github comm for - spring -
在github comm下-春季-
tips org and there you'll find the the
提示org，您会发现
authorization server that I'm using for
我正在使用的授权服务器
for this example which we've mostly
对于这个例子，我们主要
covered in a previous and so on anyway
无论如何都覆盖在先前的内容中
but then the important thing to
但是重要的是
understand is that you don't have to use
明白的是，您不必使用
the spring security OAuth authorization
Spring Security OAuth授权
server with the spring security five
Spring Security 服务器五
authorization client so we've we've got
授权客户，所以我们有
this all go off client support in spring
这一切都在春季终止了客户支持
security five we've now that we
安全五，我们现在，我们
superseded in this in this way most of
以这种方式取代了大多数
spring security ooofff that's a separate
Spring Security ooofff是独立的
project has now been folded in to spring
该项目现已展开至春季
security and because we have this client
安全，因为我们有这个客户
support we can you know we can use it
支持我们，您知道我们可以使用它吗
with spring security itself just as a
与Spring Security 本身一样
regular library inside of spring
Spring 里面的正规图书馆
security and as everything that that
安全以及一切
support doesn't need to be used with an
支持不需要与
OAuth server that we that we provide it
我们提供的OAuth服务器
can be used with any
可以与任何
ooofff server right and when you talk to
ooofff服务器权限以及与您交谈时
all of servers these days there's gonna
这些天的所有服务器都会
be at the very least there's gonna be
至少会有
ooofff usually as often as not there's
ooofff通常不存在
OAuth 2.0 but historically there have
OAuth 2.0，但从历史上看
been or auth one dot o and one dot o a
被或授权一个点o和一个点oa
and now there's two dot o and then going
现在有两个点o然后
further extending that you've got other
进一步扩展您拥有其他
sort of layered protocols if you will or
某种分层协议，如果您愿意或
layered
分层的
prescriptions for things like Oh IDC or
像IDC或
open ID connect right uh this is a
打开ID连接，对吧，这是一个
standardization of things like which
诸如此类的东西的标准化
endpoint provides the profile and they
端点提供配置文件，他们
are the name that's used to identify the
是用来识别
principal and the and the structure that
主体和的结构
comes back for the user info endpoint uh
返回用户信息端点uh
you know subtle things like this and jot
你知道像这样的微妙的事情
JWT JSON web tokens and which is this
JWT JSON Web令牌，这是
end this standardizes the the payload of
这样就标准化了
the access token itself right so a lot
访问令牌本身非常正确
of stuff here to appreciate and you'll
的东西在这里欣赏，你会
have to contend with these nuances in
必须应对这些细微差别
these different orth clients but spring
这些不同的客户，但 Spring
securities go off support the client
证券交易支持客户
support can you know manage and work
您是否知道支持和工作的支持
with all of these different types of
所有这些不同类型的
technology so you can use anything right
技术，因此您可以正确使用任何东西
and it's you can use Facebook you can
这是你可以使用Facebook，你可以
just get hub you can use Google and you
只要获得枢纽，便可以使用Google，而您
can use a third-party authorization
可以使用第三方授权
server something like octa acht as a
服务器像octa acht这样的服务器
company ok ta they're a company that
好吧，他们是一家
provides an authorization server and it
提供授权服务器
acts as a sort of hub this hub is a a
作为一种枢纽，这个枢纽是一个
it's a front-end that then delegates to
这是一个前端，然后委托给
other identity providers so you could
其他身份提供者，因此您可以
configure the hub to to talk to Active
配置集线器以与活动对话
Directory or LDAP or whatever or you can
目录或LDAP或其他任何方式
just manage it your your profiles your
只需管理您的个人资料
users in that system itself in in octa
该系统本身的用户以八进制为单位
itself either way it can vend you know
本身可以出售的方式
whatever protocol you want
您想要的任何协议
so it'll speak sam'l it'll speak o auth
所以会说sam'l它会说o auth
for the clients and so on so that's one
为客户等等，这是一个
option you could certainly use that and
选项，您当然可以使用它，并且
that's a very common choice you could
这是一个很常见的选择
also use a third-party authorization
也使用第三方授权
server so there's a key cloak from the
服务器，所以从
folks over at Red Hat which is a very
在Red Hat的人们
nice tool to use and it has good support
很好用的工具，并且有很好的支持
for spring boot apps and so on so that
用于 spring boot 应用程序等
might be worth a a future installment at
也许值得在未来分期付款
some point I think
我认为有一点
but either way key cloak and octa and
但无论哪种方式，关键披风和八角和
the spring security authorization server
Spring Security 授权服务器
and Google and Facebook and Twitter and
以及Google，Facebook和Twitter，以及
LinkedIn and literally thousands of
LinkedIn和数以千计的
other authors and servers out there all
其他所有作者和服务器
working basically the same way and you
工作方式基本上和你一样
can use them all from this new client
可以从这个新客户端使用所有这些
support so let's do that let's build a
支持，让我们这样做，让我们建立一个
Roth to client I'm going to use the arm
罗斯给客户，我要用胳膊
the Lombok compile-time annotation
Lombok编译时注释
processor will use to bring security in
处理器将用来带来安全性
the web support and I think you know
网络支持，我想你知道
that's kind of it we've already got an
就是这样，我们已经有一个
authorization server running it I think
我认为授权服务器正在运行
we do let me check
我们让我检查一下
yeah we've got it running here and the
是的，我们已经在这里运行了
important bit to understand is that I've
要了解的重要一点是，我已经
hard coded three users in this
在此硬编码三个用户
authorization server Josh Robb and Joe
授权服务器Josh Robb和Joe
obviously this is Rob winch and Joe
显然，这是罗伯·温奇和乔
grandure right Rob Rob winch is the lead
罗伯·罗伯·绞盘是领导权
of spring security and Joe granda is the
Spring Security 和乔格兰达是
sort of a lead of the efforts that
这种努力的带头人
brought in the OAuth support for spring
为春季带来了OAuth支持
security five so both of them have done
安全五，所以他们两个都做
an amazing job in this new release I'm
在这个新版本中，我的工作很棒
really grateful for all their help
非常感谢他们的帮助
they've given me in kind of making this
他们给了我一些帮助
stuff work and in my for my example here
东西工作，以我为例
today so thanks to both of them and they
今天，感谢他们俩
of course I should I should absolutely
当然我应该绝对
underscore that they would not approve
强调他们不会批准
of a default password of PW but I want
PW的默认密码，但我想要
to make it simple for my for my demo
使我的演示变得简单
here friend so I'm gonna use user name
这里的朋友，所以我要使用用户名
is Rob and Joe and Josh and password is
是Rob和Joe和Josh，密码是
PW alright don't do that at home but mix
PW不错，不要在家中那样做，但要混在一起
the demo simpler okay so we're gonna
演示更简单好了，我们要
build an oauth2 client we've generated
构建我们生成的oauth2客户端
the zip file there and I'm gonna go now
那里的zip文件，我现在去
to the Downloads directory here I'm
到这里的下载目录
gonna open this up at UA oo off to
会在UA oo上开放给
client and this client is um a you know
客户，这个客户是你知道的
it's a it's a regular web application
这是一个常规的Web应用程序
and we wanted to act as a client to our
我们想作为我们的客户
authorization server to get access to a
授权服务器以访问
resource server via the access token
通过访问令牌的资源服务器
that we get from the OAuth client
从OAuth客户端获得的
well this resource server that we're
好吧，我们这台资源服务器
gonna stand up is or that we talked to
要站起来还是我们谈话
rather is actually the authorization
实际上是授权
server as well the resource server is
服务器以及资源服务器
this is this endpoint here called
这就是这个端点
resource user info so if you're using
资源用户信息，因此，如果您正在使用
oh I DC connect there's a standardized
哦，我直流连接有一个标准化的
endpoint that the authorization server
授权服务器的端点
is supposed to expose that provides a
应该公开提供
profile well here we're going to provide
我们将在这里提供良好的配置文件
that without we're not using my DC
没有我们我们就不会使用我的DC
connector which is using OAuth here so
连接器在这里使用OAuth
we're gonna provide an endpoint here
我们将在此处提供端点
that provides a JSON structure basically
基本上提供了JSON结构
I want to take a map and serialize it
我想拍一张地图并序列化
it'll provide a JSON structure that has
它会提供一个具有
a name attribute for the principal name
主体名称的名称属性
now is this a particular interesting
现在这特别有趣
thing to get no but um you know we need
什么都没有，但是你知道我们需要
to configure that we need to configure
配置我们需要配置
that this be secured that's what this
这是安全的，这就是
bit down here does and we're saying if
有点在这里，我们是说如果
this endpoint is accessed and somebody
这个端点被访问，有人
tries to access it and doesn't have the
尝试访问它，但没有
scope profile then reject the request if
范围配置文件，然后拒绝请求，如果
it does have it
它确实有它
in return the Jason structure so I'm
作为回报杰森结构，所以我
showing us the name so you could create
向我们显示名称，以便您创建
a REST API as spring security a spring
REST API作为Spring Security 性的 Spring
REST API and then secure it using the
REST API，然后使用
spring Club security resource server
Spring Club安全资源服务器
configuration and have that then
配置，然后
delegate or reject any requests that
委托或拒绝任何要求
don't have an access token right so we
没有正确的访问令牌，所以我们
want to call this endpoint this is the
想将此端点称为
server side if you well we're gonna act
服务器端，如果您一切顺利，我们将采取行动
as a client to this endpoint right so as
作为该端点的客户端，这样
a client I want to bill to get a token
我要收费以获取代币的客户
that will allow me to make a call to
这样我就可以打电话给
this resources user info endpoint now
现在此资源用户信息端点
even though they both live in the same
即使他们都生活在同一个地方
code base and then in the same process
代码库，然后在同一过程中
they they could be two separate things
他们可能是两件分开的事
right I would just want to stress that
对，我只想强调一点
these are two logically separate things
这是两个逻辑上分开的东西
that are just happen to be running in
刚好在
this and the local machine here okay now
这个和本地机器现在还可以
in order for me to configure a client I
为了我配置客户端我
need to do some you know some yamo foo
需要做一些你知道的yamo foo
here so I need to I'm gonna go ahead and
在这里，所以我需要继续
use yamo because it's a hierarchical it
使用yamo，因为它是分层的
makes just kind of configuration just a
使只是一种配置
bit easier so I'm gonna say application
容易一点，所以我要说申请
dot llamo and there we're gonna have to
点llamo，我们将不得不
configure the spring security ooofff
配置spring安全ooofff
client registration now we talked about
现在我们谈到了客户注册
registration we have to tell our Spring
注册我们必须告诉我们的 Spring
Security client support about the
安全客户端支持有关
clients that we're gonna talk to that
我们要与之交谈的客户
we're gonna what we're gonna expect to
我们将要期待的
be able to use so we give it a logical
能够使用，所以我们给它一个逻辑
name that we care about locally login
我们关心的本地登录名
client and then we have to specify
客户，然后我们必须指定
things like the provider which is a you
像提供者这样的东西是你
know which authorizations server are we
知道我们是哪个授权服务器
using where what endpoints should we
使用我们应该在哪些端点
call for things like the the token the
要求令牌之类的东西
user info the authorization attach all
用户信息授权附上全部
these different endpoints
这些不同的端点
could change they should all produce you
可以改变他们都应该产生你
know consistently smart responses based
始终了解基于智能的响应
on the protocol of course but the
当然是在协议上
endpoints themselves may change based on
端点本身可能会根据
context paths and whatever so we have to
上下文路径以及我们必须要做的一切
spell that out now I want a state that I
现在说出我想要的状态
want to underscore that we're going to
想强调我们将要
be using a custom authorization server
使用自定义授权服务器
so I'm gonna over specify things here in
所以我要在这里指定一些东西
in common cases such as with them with
在通常情况下，例如与他们在一起
Google and github and Facebook and octa
Google和github，Facebook和octa
and so on there are already
等等，已经有
pre-configured clients for you so these
为您预配置的客户端
things like the authorization URI the
授权URI之类的东西
token your eye all that kind of stuff
标记你所有的东西
it's already pre-configured for these
已经针对这些功能进行了预配置
common cases in which case you don't
普通情况下，您不会
need to
需要
about that these providers are just
关于这些提供者只是
available for you now you can see here
现在可供您使用，您可以在这里看到
of course that I've got this this new
当然，我有这个新的
application and it's a you know it's a
应用程序，这是一个你知道这是一个
registering these types are not in the
注册这些类型不在
class path they're class path the the
他们是班级路径
tights are red my ID so that tells me
连裤袜是红色的，我的身份证号码告诉我
that we need to add a few dependencies
我们需要添加一些依赖项
here right so what we're gonna do is
在这里，所以我们要做的是
we're gonna go to the Maven palm that
我们要去Maven手掌
XML and add two bits that we care about
XML并添加我们关心的两位
here we care about the spring security
在这里，我们关心Spring 的安全性
Oh off to support goodbye to that and we
哦，支持我们再见，我们
want to also the spring security Oh off
还想 Spring 安全哦
to okay yours good all right okay so
好吧，你的好吧好吧，所以
let's see okay okay so we have those
让我们看看好吧好吧，所以我们有那些
bits on the classpath so that's that
类路径上的位，就是这样
should be it oh no oh auth - no I'm
应该是哦，不，哦，授权-不，我是
sorry that I always get there wrong Oh
对不起，我总是到那里错了哦
what - client that's what we need so
什么-客户就是我们所需要的
we're gonna add that bit
我们将添加一点
fusty I'm not sure to pronounce Jose
我不太确定该如何发音
Jose something support add that to the
何塞的支持将其添加到
classpath and common Oh off - provider
classpath和common Oh off-提供程序
well what else am I missing we have a
好吧，我还有什么想念的呢？
spring boot starter security we have the
Spring Boot Starter安全性
oauth2 client we have hole okay Jose so
oauth2客户端，我们很高兴Jose这样
we're the web support maybe we just need
我们是网络支持，也许我们只需要
to tell the idea about it may even
说出这个想法甚至
import
进口
hmm that's a bit of a bummer
嗯，这真是个无赖
oh there we go it was a cached so now
哦，我们走了，它已经被缓存了，所以现在
here are all the types that I expected
这是我所期望的所有类型
that's weird so usually ID is a bit
这很奇怪，所以通常ID有点
faster to to update itself but it seems
更新自己的速度更快，但似乎
to be okay now so good so now we go back
现在还好，所以现在我们回去
to our client configuration and that we
到我们的客户端配置，
need to tell the spring security client
需要告诉Spring 安全客户端
support about the client right so I'm
支持客户权利，所以我
gonna do that here using some
要在这里使用一些
configuration so the configuration needs
配置，因此需要配置
to point to a provider of some sort
指向某种提供者
we're going to configure that provider
我们将配置该提供程序
in a second right that provide our
在第二个权利中，
support we could actually do that you
支持我们实际上可以做到这一点
know here for example I could create a
例如，在这里知道我可以创建一个
provider section and we can come back to
提供者部分，我们可以回到
that in a second but for now or provide
一秒钟，但现在或提供
we're gonna give this a name the the
我们要给它起个名字
provider will be called local off Z and
提供者将被称为本地关闭Z和
you know reference that here we'll say
你知道参考，我们在这里说
local off Z so that's gonna be our local
Z以外的地方，所以将成为我们的地方
provider and then the client itself
提供者，然后是客户本身
there's several things we need to
我们需要做几件事
specify the ID client ID is the ID that
指定ID客户端ID是
we've registered the the client with in
我们已经在中注册了客户
the authorization server so a lot of
授权服务器很多
websites I like to like Facebook for
我喜欢Facebook的网站
example or Twitter they'll have a
例子或Twitter，他们会有一个
developer dot you know page or portal
您知道页面或门户的开发人员点
where developers can sort of
开发人员可以在那里
self-service for register clients and
为注册客户提供自助服务，以及
when they do they have to give it a
当他们这样做时，他们必须给它一个
client ID they have to give it a client
客户ID他们必须给它一个客户
secret like this so clients seek will be
这样的秘密，所以客户寻求将
just secret in this case I have to give
在这种情况下我只是秘密
it a client authentication method basic
基本的客户端身份验证方法
grant this is uh and I'm so I'm over
恩，这是我，所以我结束了
specifying a lot of stuff here right in
在这里指定很多东西
most client examples you're not gonna
大多数您不会使用的客户示例
have to specify the the authentication
必须指定身份验证
method for example you know this kind of
例如，您知道这种方法
thing a authorization code right a lot
东西授权码很多
of these are just gonna be assumed and
这些只是假设，
understood for you by default the scope
默认情况下为您理解范围
that we want is profile again if you're
我们想要的再次是个人资料
using open ID you know don't have to be
使用开放ID，您不必知道
open ID right so client name is our
正确的开放ID，因此客户名称是我们的
logical name for the client you know
您认识的客户的逻辑名称
that how we want to want it to appear in
我们想要它出现的方式
you know any other white level pages and
您知道其他任何白色级别的页面，
so on the redirect template so we have
所以在重定向模板上，我们有
to send this request to a endpoint
将此请求发送到端点
redirect
重新导向
URI template : base URL login
URI模板：基本URL登录
/o auth to for test code for slash
/ o对斜杠的测试代码进行身份验证
registration ID alright so there's our
注册ID好吧，这是我们的
redirect URI template and this endpoint
重定向URI模板和此端点
is a this is what we're expecting the
这是我们所期望的
client we're expecting the service to
客户期望我们的服务
redirect when it's done with the OAuth
使用OAuth完成后重定向
authorization flow we're gonna expect it
授权流程，我们期待
to redirect to our application and our
重定向到我们的应用程序和
application you know we're gonna fill
您知道我们要填写的应用程序
out the host imported lot you could
可以从主机进口很多
automatically filled out here for us
自动为我们填写
we'll have a filter that will listen on
我们将有一个可以监听的过滤器
login OAuth 2 code and then it'll look
登录OAuth 2代码，然后看起来
for the last bit here the path variable
最后一点是路径变量
registration ID and it's expecting that
注册ID，并且期望
to match this login client okay so you
匹配这个登录客户端好吧，所以你
have those bits there now we need to go
现在有那些位了，我们需要去
back and configure that provider so
返回并配置该提供程序，以便
authorial uri is gonna be equal to http
uri等于http
off server : 8090 now i've got that
服务器外：8090现在我已经知道了
running application I told you I've got
我告诉你我正在运行的应用程序
this application running on the same
该应用程序在同一台上运行
host and port right so if you you see
主机和端口正确，所以如果您看到
here ping off server I've got that
在这里ping服务器我已经知道了
running on I've got Etsy hosts I just
在我拥有的Etsy主机上运行
got a little line in my Ipsy hosts that
在我的Ipsy主持人中有一线
points to all servers so here it says
指向所有服务器，所以在这里说
one two seven zero zero one localhost
一二七零零一本地主机
off server and then I've got another
服务器，然后我有另一个
domain here as well but the reason I
域也是如此，但我的原因
have it a separate domain a separate
有一个单独的域一个单独的
host name is because the spring security
主机名是因为spring安全
authorization server is going to provide
授权服务器将提供
cookies and so are the so is the spring
饼干， Spring 也是如此
security client right so that client is
安全客户端权限，以便客户端
gonna have a cookie and so as the
要有一个饼干，所以
authorization server and remember
授权服务器并记住
cookies are keyed by the host name not
Cookies不是由主机名键入的
the port but the host name so if you
端口，但主机名，如果您
have two different cookies coming from
有两个不同的Cookie来自
the same host they might you know
他们可能认识的同一个主机
trample one another so we want to make
彼此践踏，所以我们想
sure that they're separate hosts now to
确保他们现在是单独的主机
avoid that problem right so it doesn't
避免那个问题吧，所以不会
have to actually be a you know DNS host
必须实际上是一个您知道的DNS主机
it can just be Etsy host for example
例如，它可以只是Etsy主机
which is DNS but I mean it doesn't have
这是DNS，但我的意思是它没有
to be complicated right very very simple
非常复杂，非常非常简单
to get this working so okay
使这个工作正常
we've now we've got to provide the
我们现在必须提供
authorizations URI so in our case the
授权URI，因此在本例中
authorization server has the OAuth
授权服务器具有OAuth
authorized endpoint
授权端点
the token URI is that's just copy and
令牌URI就是复制并
paste some of this here okay
在这里粘贴一些
and the off server token your eye is off
和关闭服务器令牌，您的视线就关闭了
token and the user info URI is off sorry
令牌，并且用户信息URI关闭对不起
its resources user info so this is the
它的资源用户信息，所以这是
end point that we're gonna we're going
终点，我们要去
to call later on that has them the this
稍后再打电话给他们这个
is the resource server that's the bit
是资源服务器
that we care about that's non-standard
我们在乎那是非标准的
in our case but would be for example if
在我们的情况下，但例如
using oh I DC so user name attribute and
我使用DC，所以用户名属性和
that's the name that we get back from
那是我们从中得到的名字
the JSON stanza that we expect to be
我们期望成为的JSON节
able to identify the principal so Rob or
能够识别主体，所以Rob或
Joe or
乔或
or gosh okay so now let's run this
还是天哪，所以现在让我们运行
application this is we have nothing
应用程序这是我们一无所有
written in code we've done absolutely
用代码写的我们绝对做到了
nothing in terms of code but already we
就代码而言什么也没有，但是我们已经
should have a valid client so let's just
应该有一个有效的客户，所以让我们
see if that starts up without issue and
看看是否启动没有问题，并且
then we'll use that that configuration
然后我们将使用该配置
do or work oh okay that looks ok so
做或工作哦，好的，看起来不错，所以
looks like we've got a filter chain
看起来我们有一个过滤链
we've got a default username and
我们有一个默认的用户名，
password okay so good so that's that
密码还不错，就是这样
would seem to be all we need for our our
似乎就是我们需要的一切
client now again you could have as many
现在又有客户
registrations as you want you could have
您想要的注册
a full client and you know so on you
一个完整的客户，你也知道
could have made registrations for
本来可以注册的
clients and for providers as you'd like
客户和您想要的提供者
in the CMO file and of course this stuff
在CMO文件中，当然还有
could be loaded from a database of
可以从数据库中加载
course there's an interface so this is
当然有一个界面，所以这是
ultimately these registrations these
最终这些注册这些
client registrations get turned into
客户注册变成
objects of just that type registration
该类型注册的对象
right this is a a this is the property
对，这是一个，这是财产
sorry it's a it's called client
抱歉，这是一个所谓的客户
registration here we are
在这里注册
client registration blah blah blah and
客户注册等等等等
clients configured condition where are
客户端配置条件在哪里
the beam it so it gets mapped into a
它的光束，所以它映射到一个
in-memory client repository and we have
内存中的客户端存储库，我们有
objects of type client registration
客户注册类型的对象
right so where are those bits that's um
对，那么这些位在哪里
I'm not inspired by
我没有受到启发
IntelliJ is not seeing these types so
IntelliJ没有看到这些类型，所以
let's make sure I've got the right types
确保我有正确的类型
on the class path here again spring sick
在上课的路上，这又春暖花开
Oh Centron security I knew I did
哦，我知道我做了Centron安全
something obviously wrong okay okay
明显有问题，好吧好吧
there we are so it's actually spring
在那里，所以实际上是 Spring
security here I'm all excited about the
安全在这里，我都为之兴奋
merged support for spring security OAuth
对Spring Security OAuth的合并支持
in spring security and I and I go and
在Spring Security 中，我和我去了
give it the wrong group ID pointing to
给它指定错误的组ID
the old spring security auth group ID
旧的Spring安全身份验证组ID
don't do that it's actually spring
不要这样做，实际上是 Spring
security oh okay so now client
安全哦，好吧，现在客户端
registration which actually that
注册实际上
invalidates my previous run so let's go
使我之前的跑步无效，让我们开始吧
ahead and run that application again
继续并再次运行该应用程序
this time and while that's happening
这次，而这正在发生
let's see if client registrations on the
让我们看看是否客户注册在
path but there we are okay so our
路径，但是我们还可以，所以我们
previous run did not work good that
以前的运行效果不好
means that there's a beam of type that
表示有一束光束
we haven't configured authorization URI
我们尚未配置授权URI
can't be empty okay so that's the error
不能为空好吧，这就是错误
that we have there we need to configure
我们在那里需要配置
authorization your I fix the typo all
授权您我全部打错
right so that looks like it's happy good
对，看起来好像很幸福
and we got the right types on the class
我们在课堂上得到了正确的类型
path and it's it hasn't printed out a
路径，它还没有打印出
default username password which means
默认的用户名密码
that spring security has detected the
Spring Security已检测到
OAuth stuff so that's all very good and
OAuth的东西，所以一切都很好，
we can actually now go back to that type
我们现在实际上可以回到该类型
that I was gonna show you a second ago
我要第二次告诉你
client registration and here we just
客户注册，我们在这里
have a type a type that produces you
具有产生你的类型
know that holds things like the
知道拥有像
registration I need a client ID the
注册我需要一个客户ID
client secret etc all of these are you
客户秘密等所有这些都是你
know this is also you can see the
知道这也是你可以看到的
default is basic an ID uh for example so
默认是一个基本的ID，例如
a lot of this stuff is kind of obvious
很多这样的东西是显而易见的
you can register custom client
您可以注册自定义客户端
registrations if you want right there's
注册，如果你想对的话
actually a client registration
实际上是客户注册
repository and that repository is the
仓库，那个仓库就是
thing that must be aware of your client
必须了解您的客户的事情
registrations but there's no reason that
注册，但没有理由
this client client registration
此客户客户注册
repository has to be the default one you
存储库必须是您的默认存储库
could have one that's based on a
可能有一个基于
database for example okay so a lot of
例如数据库好很多
different options here
这里有不同的选择
different interfaces that you could use
您可以使用的不同接口
to to make this work easier now we have
为了使这项工作更容易
that auto configuration and spring boot
自动配置和Spring 启动
which we're using to to take your
我们用来带你
properties and to turn them into
属性并将其变成
configuration but there's absolutely no
配置，但绝对没有
reason that you um you know that you
你嗯，你知道你的原因
have to do it that way all right now
现在必须那样做
moving on so we're gonna build an
继续前进，我们将建立一个
application and we're gonna talk to that
应用程序，我们将与之交谈
REST API we're gonna talk to that
REST API，我们要谈谈
resource server the profile endpoint
资源服务器配置文件端点
using our newly minted access tokens
使用我们新创建的访问令牌
which we have to obtain so let's go
我们必须获得的，所以让我们开始吧
ahead and try and do this let's create a
继续尝试并做到这一点，让我们创建一个
resting point here on the client called
客户在这里的休息点叫
class profile rest controller okay and
类配置文件其余控制器好，并且
we're gonna create an endpoint here that
我们将在此处创建一个端点
returns just the details that come back
仅返回返回的详细信息
from the profiling point now that detail
从分析的角度来看，现在的细节
is just gonna be a class class principal
只是成为班主任
details I'm gonna have a field here a
详细信息，我将在此处创建一个字段
string name and you know I can use
字符串名称，您知道我可以使用
Lombok here to make short work of this
龙目岛在这里做这个简短的工作
so no aren't constructor alright so
所以没有构造函数不是吗
there's my very very simple type I'm
我的类型非常简单
gonna return the principal details when
何时返回主要详细信息
somebody logs in so details or a profile
有人登录，因此详细信息或个人资料
okay and in order to do this work we're
好的，为了完成这项工作，我们
gonna take advantage of the oauth2
会利用oauth2的优势
authentication token so here's my token
身份验证令牌，这是我的令牌
that gets injected that's the principal
被注射是主要的
that will be hydrated by the time the
到时候水化
same point gets called so the first time
同一点被叫，所以第一次
around when this application starts up
该应用程序启动时
we're gonna hit this endpoint and it's
我们要达到这个终点，
gonna redirect to the login filter you
将重定向到您的登录过滤器
know we direct to the off server so
知道我们直接到离线服务器，所以
we'll never hit this endpoint without
如果没有我们，我们将永远无法达到目标
this token it'll it'll force us to to
这个令牌，它将迫使我们
redirect and authenticate okay
重定向和验证还可以
so what we're gonna do is we're gonna
所以我们要做的是
take advantage of the token to get the
利用令牌获得
to get the access token so we've got an
获取访问令牌，所以我们有一个
authentication token we'll use that to
身份验证令牌，我们将使用它来
get the access token in order for us to
获取访问令牌以便我们进行
do that work we need to use the auth to
做这项工作，我们需要使用auth来
authorize client service so private
授权客户服务如此私密
final or auth to authorize client
最终或授权授权客户端
service injecting this into the
服务注入到
application and we'll say return this
应用程序，我们会说返回这个
dot client service dot load authorize
点客户端服务点负载授权
client and we use the token get
客户，我们使用令牌获取
authorize client registration ID token
授权客户注册ID令牌
dot get name
点获取名称
and this gives us a a client service or
这为我们提供了客户服务或
I'll throw its client rather and the
我宁愿丢给它的客户，
client we can use here let's clean this
我们可以在这里使用的客户端让我们清理一下
up a little bit we can use the client to
一点点，我们可以使用客户端来
then ascertain information about the
然后确定有关
application so the user info URI we can
应用程序，以便我们可以提供用户信息URI
get that from the client ID so client
从客户端ID获取，以便客户端
client get client registration dot get
客户获取客户注册点获取
provide our details dot get user info
提供我们的详细信息点获取用户信息
your endpoint that's the endpoint that
您的端点就是
we want to there's to call so we're
我们想打电话给我们
getting the URI here of the user info
在此处获取用户信息的URI
endpoint okay so that's the URI and now
端点好，所以这是URI，现在
we need to to make a request with this
我们需要对此提出要求
client with this information from the
客户从
user and for your eye we're gonna make a
用户，为了您的眼睛，我们将
request to that but we need to have the
要求，但我们需要
token in order to do that so we can we
为了做到这一点，我们可以
need to have the access token to do that
需要具有访问令牌才能执行此操作
so we could we could in this code in
所以我们可以在这段代码中
line you know obtain access token and
您知道的行获取访问令牌并
then configure a risk template call and
然后配置风险模板调用并
it should be a request entity you know
它应该是一个您知道的请求实体
we can configure that here manually if
我们可以在这里手动配置
we wanted to but instead I would prefer
我们想要，但我宁愿
to change the rest template that we use
更改我们使用的其余模板
we're gonna make a call using a rest
我们要休息一下打个电话
template so let's configure the rest
模板，让我们配置其余的
template and then inject that into the
模板，然后将其注入
constructor so let's configure a rest
构造函数，让我们配置一个休息
I'm put up here and use that rest
我放在这里休息
template to make a call and it's secured
进行呼叫的模板，它是安全的
way so I'm gonna say new rest template
这样我要说新的休息模板
builder interceptors we're gonna provide
我们将提供的建筑拦截器
a Interceptor and the intercept that
拦截器和拦截器
we're gonna provide is a client HTTP
我们要提供的是客户端HTTP
request interceptor and the code that
请求拦截器和代码
we're gonna use it's fairly
我们将使用它相当
straightforward again we're gonna also
再简单一点，我们也会
inject that off to authorize client
注入以授权客户
service o auth to authorize client
服务或授权以授权客户端
service and the filter is fairly
服务和过滤器是相当
straightforward right so we would say
直截了当的权利，所以我们会说
take the client request execution say
带客户请求执行说
execution dot execute HTTP request by
执行点通过执行HTTP请求
its etc and we're gonna respond we're
它的等等，我们要回应我们
going to go ahead and now
现在要继续
add a token and an access token to the
将令牌和访问令牌添加到
headers of the request that's being sent
正在发送的请求的标头
by this rest template okay so well we'll
通过这个其余的模板好吧，我们会
use well first of all get access to the
首先使用好获得访问
current authorized authentication token
当前授权的认证令牌
token right off to dot class typecast
令牌直接用于点类转换
and we're gonna look at these current
我们将看看这些最新的
you know static you know reference to
你知道静态你知道引用
the current token right the context
当前令牌正确的上下文
local token and we're gonna cast it to
当地令牌，我们将其投放到
author an oauth2 authentication token
编写一个oauth2认证令牌
now this is probably not the smartest
现在这可能不是最聪明的
thing to do this may t be this might be
要做的事情可能是
a different token when you use it so if
使用其他令牌时，如果
you have different types of
你有不同类型的
authentication possible in the
可以在
application you should definitely do of
您绝对应该做的应用程序
an instance of before you do this but in
在执行此操作之前的一个实例，但是在
my case I know that unequivocally it's
我的情况我清楚地知道
gonna be an auth to authentication token
将成为身份验证令牌的身份验证
now I've got this token and from there I
现在我有了这个令牌，从那里我
want to get the client so I can do the
想得到客户，所以我可以做
same as before I'll say auth to
和以前一样，我将对auth说
authorize client equals CS lower to
授权客户将CS降低至
authorize client and I'm gonna use the
授权客户，我将使用
token get get the authorized
令牌获取获得授权
registration ID token don't get a name
注册ID令牌没有名称
and then we use the headers we're going
然后我们使用标题
to change the headers will say HTTP
更改标题会说HTTP
headers dot add or set authorization I
标头点添加或设置授权I
guess we can add it ourselves add HTTP
猜想我们可以自己添加它，添加HTTP
headers dot to authorization bearer plus
标头点到授权载体加上
the client access token so client dot
客户端访问令牌，因此客户端点
get an access token dot get value token
获取访问令牌点获取值令牌
value all right so there's our custom
珍惜一切，所以有我们的习惯
header you know custom bared header and
标头，您知道自定义裸标头和
we're gonna then proceed with the
我们将继续
request disk of course disk of course
当然要磁盘
can be replaced with a lambda so there
可以用lambda代替，所以在那里
we go there's our rest template and it
我们去那里是我们的休息模板，
is going to you know look up the current
会知道您要查找当前
authentication token we have to be this
身份验证令牌，我们必须是这个
manually right I'm doing this using the
手动对，我正在使用
security context holder here because we
安全上下文持有者在这里，因为我们
have a beam being process outside of a
有光束在
request you notice that I can get access
要求您注意我可以访问
to that same token as a argument result
与相同的标记作为参数结果
as a resolve argument in my spring MVC
作为我春季MVC中的解决论点
handler method so this works just fine
处理程序方法，所以工作正常
if I wanted to write that code here but
如果我想在这里写那个代码，但是
if I want to get access to it
如果我想访问它
independently I can do the same thing as
独立地，我可以做与
well because it is ultimately just
好吧，因为它最终只是
coming from this security context older
来自此安全上下文较旧
dot get context that
点获取上下文
occasion all right so now let's see we
有时候好吧，现在让我们看看
have this configuration I have the
有这个配置我有
client here and I have the URL now I'll
客户在这里，我现在有了URL，我将
write that I want to write that request
写我要写那个请求
to the downstream serves on make that
下游服务使
request to the downstream service so
向下游服务要求
I'll say this doctor does template.dot
我会说这个医生做template.dot
and we're gonna use the exchange and
我们将使用交易所和
we're gonna say that we want to make a
我们会说我们想做一个
call to the user
打电话给用户
URI these are info your eye it's gonna
URI这些是您所要注意的信息
be an HTTP GET call there's no body so
是HTTP GET调用，没有任何内容，因此
we'll say no and then the type of data
我们先说不，然后再说数据类型
that we want to come back is a type
我们想要回来的是一种
principal details so let's see what we
主要细节，让我们看看我们
get when we save all this response okay
得到，当我们保存所有这些响应好吗
so I'm gonna say I just turn spuntz
所以我要说我只是转弯
entity get body alright there's our call
实体让身体好起来，这是我们的电话
not bad and you know that's a basically
不错，你知道这基本上是
I'll take so let's go ahead and see what
我接受，让我们继续前进，看看有什么
it looks like when we run it in 10 okay
它看起来像当我们在10中运行它时
so we've got a filter at a rest template
所以我们在其余模板上有一个过滤器
that's been customized here we've got a
这是自定义的，我们有一个
filter it's it's awfully R so it'll make
过滤它是可怕的R所以它会
off attenti gated calls we might we
关闭attenti门控电话，我们可能会
might rewrite this code to say oh well
可能会改写这段代码说好
if you don't have this then just you
如果你没有这个，那就只有你
know return a regular just execute so we
知道返回一个常规只是执行，所以我们
could actually say if this is no lure or
实际上可以说这是否没有诱惑力，或者
something like that if there's no
如果没有的话
authentication then then you know just
身份验证，然后您知道
proceed without it right so it could be
没有正确的继续前进，所以可能
a regular rest template and we'll just
一个常规的休息模板，我们将
skip all the getting headers and adding
跳过所有获取标题并添加
them and so on okay all right so the
他们等等，好吧，所以
applications up and running on port 8080
应用程序在端口8080上启动并运行
localhost 8080 for slash forward slash
斜线正斜杠的localhost 8080
and we hit login client now notice that
现在我们点击登录客户端，注意
I am now I was on the when I when I go
我现在在去的时候
back to this page localhost 8080 for
返回此页localhost 8080
touch login even though I hit enter
即使我按Enter也可以触摸登录
- for - it redirected to login now if I
-对于-如果我重定向到现在登录
click on this it says login client right
点击它说登录客户端正确
this is the logical name that we gave
这是我们给的逻辑名称
you know in the configuration though the
你知道在配置中
client name not the client ID the client
客户名称而不是客户ID客户
ID is localhost 8080 for session off -
会话关闭的ID为localhost 8080-
for session authorization for session
用于会话授权
log in client when I click on this it's
当我点击它时登录客户端
going to redirect to the authorization
将重定向到授权
server right that filter is looking at
过滤器正在查看的服务器权
the request and saying oh you want me to
请求，说哦，你要我
redirect you to the authorization server
将您重定向到授权服务器
which lives on host and port off -
住在主机和港口附近-
server colon 80 90 so different host you
服务器冒号80 90如此不同的主机
can see it's a different server I'm
可以看到我是另一台服务器
using the white label pages for both the
将白色标签页用于
authorization server and for the client
授权服务器和客户端
right so both are just a very very sort
对，所以两者都非常好
of
的
uninteresting pages you can and should
您可以并且应该无趣的页面
customize these to match the skin that
自定义这些以匹配皮肤
your application is expecting okay so
您的应用程序期望可以，所以
here remember we've got Joe and password
这里记得我们有乔和密码
is PW all right so that's it login it's
是PW没事吧，就是登录了
asking me do I want to allow or to
问我我要允许还是要
authorize client one two three four to
授权客户一二三四
access my protected resources this might
访问我的受保护资源，这可能
be the you know the equivalent of the
是你知道的相当于
Facebook friend page or the Facebook
Facebook好友页面或Facebook
page which says you want to allow this
页面上说你想允许这个
third-party website to have your profile
第三方网站拥有您的个人资料
your friend graph you know whatever and
你的朋友图你知道
you can see this is you know valid flow
你可以看到这是你知道有效的流量
valid oil flow here but the
有效油流量在这里，但
authorization this is part of a month
授权，这是一个月的一部分
the authentication is non-standard right
认证是非标准的权利
the authentication I just happened to
我刚遇到的身份验证
login using and it should be formed on
登录使用，它应该形成
my authorization server but that isn't
我的授权服务器，但这不是
you know that's not necessarily the same
你知道不一定是一样的
thing is um oh wow that's not a lot
嗯，哇，那不是很多
that's helped I could have logged in any
这可以帮助我登录任何
number of different ways and then
一些不同的方式，然后
redirected back to this OAuth flow okay
重定向回此OAuth流程，可以
so let's say authorize and there we go I
所以说授权然后我们走了
redirected me back to this to the client
将我重定向回客户端
I hit the four slash endpoint and we got
我击中了四个斜线端点，我们得到了
the profile information right so I'm
个人资料信息正确，所以我
logged in and now whenever I make a
登录，现在每当我创建一个
request you know if I make any requests
要求您知道我是否提出任何要求
in this endpoint and I use that rest
在这个端点，我用剩下的
template it's going to add this header
模板，它将添加此标头
and this header will authenticate me so
这个标题会验证我的身份
now I can call any other API that
现在我可以调用任何其他API
expects any other resource server that
需要任何其他资源服务器
expects that token and it'll work
期望该令牌，它将起作用
alright now we've looked at some of the
好了，现在我们看了一些
client support in spring security five
Spring Security 五中的客户支持
we looked at how to configure one you
我们研究了如何配置一个
know fill out everything how to
知道填写一切如何
configure everything that you know you
配置您了解的所有内容
don't have it we couldn't take anything
没有它，我们什么也拿不了
for granted so we click we configured
理所当然，因此我们单击配置
the provider and the client itself and
提供者和客户本身以及
could configure all the details and
可以配置所有详细信息，
hopefully you you won't have to do this
希望你不必这样做
more than more than once or twice right
不止一次或两次以上
you can get it right it can also be can
你可以做到正确，也可以
convenient to - you know configure a
方便-您知道配置
filter and configure rest template and
过滤和配置其余模板，以及
put this in auto configuration and you
将其置于自动配置中，您
might even have information about which
甚至可能有关于哪个的信息
auth clients to call being loaded from a
验证客户端以从中加载呼叫
database for example so there's no
例如数据库，所以没有
reason that this couldn't be just
原因可能不只是
automatic you have an out
自动你出去了
that talks to a a well-known database
与知名数据库对话
maybe in your organization and you have
也许在您的组织中
the right auto configuration on the
正确的自动配置
classpath and and then when it when it
classpath然后再当它的时候
starts up it'll connect and you know
启动它将连接，您知道
you'll have automatically authenticated
您将自动进行身份验证
risk templates able to talk to these
能够与这些对话的风险模板
resources you know using the
您使用的资源
authorization server so all that can be
授权服务器，以便所有
very very easy I did the hard way here
非常非常容易，我在这里做了艰苦的努力
and I expect that we'll eventually have
我希望我们最终会
the ability to just this will just be
做到这一点的能力将是
automatically contributed for you going
自动为您贡献
forward I expect that this is one of the
向前，我希望这是其中之一
things that will be nice to have going
事情会很高兴
forward there is actually an OAuth rest
向前实际上有一个OAuth休息
template for example from spring
例如 Spring 的模板
security off but increasingly that is
安全关闭，但越来越多的是
less and less useful right it'll be nice
越来越少用了吧，这会很好
just be able to have a filter
只是可以有一个过滤器
automatically contributed to my regular
自动为我的定期捐款
arrest template like this so we looked
像这样逮捕模板，所以我们看了看
at the spring security 5 I looked at
我看了Spring Security 5
configuring custom clients we looked at
配置我们研究过的自定义客户端
configuring everything that you need to
配置所需的一切
talk to an authorization server a custom
与授权服务器交谈自定义
authorization server like the spring
春季授权服务器
security
安全
ooofff based authorization server which
基于ooofff的授权服务器
underpins UA and Cloud Foundry and we've
支持UA和Cloud Foundry，我们已经
also looked at how this is just one of
还看着这只是其中之一
many choices and you could look at the
很多选择，你可以看看
common Oh F - provider definitions here
常见的哦F-这里的提供者定义
and you'll see that they're you know
你会看到他们是你知道的
common ones already provided for you so
常见的已经提供给您
you don't have to to worry about that if
您不必担心，如果
you are just connecting to one of these
您只是连接到其中之一
big big four with more to come I'm sure
我相信还有更多的大四巨头
we also looked at you know how to use
我们也看着你知道如何使用
the API how to use the the API itself
API如何使用API​​本身
ease the OAuth to authorize client there
简化OAuth以在那里授权客户端
off to authorize client service
授权客户服务
these are API is there in spring
这些是春季的API
security itself and they give you kind
安全本身，他们给你一种
of a repository a runtime api api that
存储库的运行时api api
you can interact with to understand
您可以进行互动以了解
which clients you've got and - you know
您拥有哪些客户-您知道
interrogate them and get the information
询问他们并获取信息
about them so all this is managed for
关于他们，所以这一切都为
you by the framework and there's a
你的框架，有一个
default in-memory version but that could
默认的内存版本，但是可以
of course be based on the database we
当然要基于我们的数据库
haven't really looked at testing for
并没有真正考虑测试
example so testing is a thing that you
例如，测试就是你要做的事情
can and should do ultimately when you
最终可以并且应该在您
write this test this test is going to be
写这个测试，这个测试将是
you know using the standard spring MVC
你知道使用标准的spring MVC
mockingly C test client and there you
嘲笑C测试客户端，在那里
have a builder there's a some test
有一个建造者，有一些测试
filter there's some tests some static
过滤有一些测试一些静态
methods available on
可用的方法
I type in spring security that gives you
我输入Spring Security 性给您
the ability to say okay run this mock
可以说的能力运行此模拟
client request with this current
客户要求与此当前
authentication and you can easily mock
身份验证，您可以轻松模拟
out this authentication token and then
出这个认证令牌，然后
you know when you're when you test your
你知道你什么时候测试
code when you test your endpoints it'll
测试端点时的代码
have access to that token this all this
可以访问令牌
code will still work it'll just be a you
代码仍然有效，只是您一个
know a mock token alright my friends
我的朋友知道一个模拟令牌
with that I hope you got something out
希望你能有所收获
of this thanks for watching and we'll
感谢您的收看，我们将
see you next time
下次见
you
您